Online Grievance Redressal System
This is the Login Panel Here we can log into different types of User.
This is student registration page where students can register their account.
Lets log in to a student account
Enter Student ID and Password
This is student Dashboard
From Sidebar  you can go to Complain->My Complain to check your previous complains and their status.
You can also  create a new complain.
Complain Type
Complain Title
Complain Details
Complain Department
Upload Files
Lets check the complain we just created.
You can View the complain details and chat with the department
Logging Out
Log in as Department
Department Dashboard
Department Admin can view all students and update & delete their profile.
Department Can also add new students
Department can view all the complains and reply to their complains